SYIFA AINUN ALBAR

+62-853-3688-2008 · ainunalbar@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/syifaai Surabaya, Indonesia 60128

ABOUT ME

I am a graduate of the Surabaya State Electronics Polytechnic from the Diploma 3 Informatics Engineering Study Program. During my studies, I have gained a basic understanding of various programming languages. I also have knowledge in the field of user interface design (UI/UX), which helps me understand the importance of an intuitive and engaging user experience. In addition, I have studied basic networking concepts, which allows me to understand and handle connectivity issues and network infrastructure. My academic experience includes practical projects involving application development, system design, and implementation of technology solutions. I have strong analytical skills and enjoy solving complex technical problems. I also have a passion for continuous learning and self-development in the field of information technology. I believe that the combination of technical knowledge, analytical skills, and a desire to continue learning makes me ready to contribute in a dynamic professional environment.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Dynamic - OutBound - Mojoketo, Indonesia

Jan 2023

Transportation Division

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Web E-Learning - Surabaya, Indonesia

Nov 2022

Front-End Development

Project web developing for e-learning

- Developed a website using PHP with the laravel framework
- Create admin Dashboard along with user database using MySQL
- Create responsive Website
- Implementation Website full CRUD

Mobile Application Handphone Catalogue - Surabaya, Indonesia

Apr 2023

Mobile Flutter Development

An application to monitor the latest cellphone developments and prices

SIM Ticketing Kereta Api - Surabaya, Indonesia

Nov 2022

Front-End Development

This website is used to book train tickets

- Developed using PHP Native
- Create a table that includes the passenger master, train master, ticket purchase transactions
- Database Using MySQL

Application MasBro Canteen - Surabaya, Indonesia

Mobile Flutter Development

Project developing a food ordering application for the PENS cafetatia using the Agile Scrum Framework

- · Create a frame for the splash screen
- Create a button that connects to another frame
- · Create a search field that filters according to what you are looking for

Web Portofolio - Surabaya, Indonesia

Jul 2024

Feb 2023 - Now

Front-End Development

Contains a portfolio of projects that have been done.

Web Portal Client - Surabaya, Indonesia

Nov 2023 - Des 2023

Front-End Development

Create a website so that clients can control the website or mobile application that is being ordered at PT. Webcare Digital Indonesia

- Create UI/UX Design
- · Create an admin dashboard and client dashboard display

Application My PENS - Surabaya, Indonesia

Jan 2024 - Jun 2024

Mobile Flutter Development

This project is a final assignment project during college. In this project, we developed a monitoring system for students who are currently studying MBKM and included it in the My PENS application

- · Create UI/UX Design
- Connecting to an API endpoint
- Developing a display based on the UI that has been compiled

Application My Mitra - Surabaya, Indonesia

Jan 2024 - Jun 2024

Mobile Flutter Development

This project is also part of the final assignment during college, the difference is that this project is specifically for monitoring campus partners, therefore a special application called My Mitra was created.

- Create UI/UX Design
- Connecting to an API endpoint
- · Developing a display based on the UI that has been compiled

Web Wordpress - Surabaya, Indonesia

Aug 2023 - Des 2023

Wordpress Development

Develop a website built using WordPress

EDUCATION

Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya - Surabaya, Indonesia

Aug 2021- Jul 2024

Informatics Engineering

SMK Barunawati - Surabaya, Indonesia

Aug 2018 - May 2021

Computer and Network Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. OPMC - Surabaya, Indonesia Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

Apprenticeship

PT. Agrodana Futures - indonesia Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

Marketing

PT. Webcare Digital Indonesia - indonesia Jul 2023 - Des 2023

Web Developer - Apprenticeship

SKILLS, ACHIEVEMENTS & OTHER EXPERIENCE

Soft Skills: Team Work, Humble, Responsibility, Problem Solving, Growth Mindset

Hard Skills: Flutter, UI/UX Design, Project Management, Wordpress, Laravel, HTML, CSS

Project (2022): Web E-Learning

Project (2022): SIM Ticketing Kereta Api

Project (2023) : Application Handphone Catalogue

Project (2023): Application MasBro Canteen

Project (2023): Web Portal Client PT.Webcare Digital Indonesia

Project (2024): Web Portofolio

Project (2024): Application Monitoring MBKM Mitra

Project (2024): Application Monitoring MBKM

Project (2024) : Web Wordpress **Achievement** (2024) : TOEFL